# Fejiro Abere

Ughelli North, Delta, Nigeria



aberefejiro@gmail.com



+2348075853868



linkedin.com/in/fejiro-abere-487b08161

# Summary

I am an undergraduate at the University of Benin, Nigeria. Currently studying Computer Engineering in my final year. I have 1+ years of experience in Front-end development.

I am a fast learner and love learning new things (currently learning algorithm and data structures) and achieving what I aim for with enthusiasm, with hopes of building myself as a front end developer.

I am able and ready to rise up to any challenge thrown at me.

I want to use what I have learnt and will learn to improve myself and my country if possible and also be an inspiration to women that want to venture into tech.

# **Experience**



#### Web Developer Internship

Afriportal Network Limited

May 2021 - Aug 2021 (4 months)

Underwent training as a front end developer in compliance with my internship program

### Associate Android Developer

Google Africa Developers Scholarship

Nov 2020 - Mar 2021 (5 months)

Learned more about android development using Pluralsight and did my certification exam.

# Mobile developer

HNG Internship

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020 (3 months)

- -My team and I created the mobile app MedBuzz (with the app you can create reminders for drugs you are taking so you won't forget them) which is currently available on google playstore.
- -Out of 11,000 people who entered the internship from around the world, I finished as one of the 200+ finalists.



#### **Mobile Application Developer**

start.ng

Feb 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

#### Education



#### 🕍 University of Benin

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering

Jan 2016 - Aug 2022

# Presentation National High School

High School Diploma 2009 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Start.ng Software Development Training start.ng SNG02376
- Mobile Developer HNG Internship HNG02591
- Java (Basic) HackerRank 3E7285A224DA

## **Skills**

Web Development • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Git • GitHub • React.js • GreenSock Animation Platform (GSAP) • Next.js • JSON